that's a fun job i grew up i never knew
i'd be a comedian i grew up a pretty
awkward kid i was painfully shy
and the people always don't know what
the w is about what's johnny w it's
short for my last name i just shortened
it make it easier for everybody i have a
hard to pronounce
last name so i just shortened it down
make it easier my last name is baxter
and uh no my last name is weddington
which seems easy weddington but i get
washington and wellington and
liechtenstein that's a weird one the
worst was third grade i was in a new
school anybody have a hard to pronounce
last name here you know my pain if the
teacher gets it wrong call and roll
you're gonna get mocked the whole year
she gets to the w's i'm sending her
telepathic messages please get it right
i can't deal
weddington wedding cause she's like all
right walker okay watson
okay way a ton
way a ton on the back can i just head
home now and develop an eating disorder
thanks so much
you're the greatest
was a chubby kid in middle school for
sure had asthma you may have asthma here
tonight hold your inhalers high don't be
ashamed
i love the asthma it was great man that
little asthma note from my doctor that
was my get out of gym free cards what
that was
just hand it over there you go that's
your copy okay it's laminated yeah i got
lots more
i'm gonna have a seat oh we're climbing
the big rope today i don't think so
i will not be getting friction burns on
my crotch i'm going to have a seat
and wheeze to myself that was 8th grade
then 9th grade came suddenly it was the
high school p.e teacher
he wasn't having it what is this asthma
i can cure asthma
i was like you can what his cure for
asthma
he made me run what's called suicides do
you guys know what that is suicides
it's a horrifying series of wind sprints
they call it i don't know who named that
but let me tell you something
if you make a little fat kid run back
and forth until he dies that is homicide
that is not
they will prosecute you pretty sure
[Applause]
but that wasn't even the worst day in
gym class by far the worst day was the
first gym class of 10th grade that was
the day of the president's physical
fitness challenge
do they do that here they got to stop
it's like the hunger games
he'd line us up everybody take a minute
get a buddy we're going to time each
other everybody take a minute get
yourself a butt it's like i don't need a
minute i don't have a buddy okay
i'm the shyest kid here i look up
everybody's got a buddy but me i'm
mortified i look at the end of the
bleachers there's a girl sitting by
herself i don't even know her is she
even in my class but it doesn't matter
because they're not gonna put a girl
with me they did
come on down here sally it's fine you'll
be with johnny come on now you're going
to time johnny okay he's going to do
push-ups from any time
count the jumping jacks you're going to
count them timing me now
then you're going to hold his feet
and he gonna do sit-ups for a minute
yeah that turned pretty quickly into a
game of how many times can johnny fart
into the face of a stranger
before she begins to cry
and the answer is 17 17 times oh it's
the number of times
i like being a kid other than that story
uh i like to be a kid growing up man
it's fun stuff at church now kids have
all the cool stuff you church man trunk
or treat
anybody heard of that trunk or tree i
didn't know what this was my church did
it i was so excited man reach our
community whatever
it was awesome watching my pastor
explain it to the older people the week
before
he gets on the mic now we know we don't
live in the same time we grew up in
we can't be out there knocking on
strange people's doors it's not safe
what we're gonna do we're gonna get all
the automobiles in the parking lot
in the dark decorate them we're gonna
teach kids that car
trunks may be full of delicious candy
hallelujah where
where'd everybody go
[Laughter]
you